module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What board game involves a game piece called a "Bread Basket"?', 
    a: 'Clue',
    b: 'Stratego',
    c: 'Mouse Trap',
    d: 'Operation',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a character from McDonald\'s "McDonaldland"?', 
    a: 'Captain Crook',
    b: 'Billy Burger',
    c: 'Grimace',
    d: 'Birdie',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Paul McCartney\'s daughter Stella, is famous in what industry?', 
    a: 'Fashion',
    b: 'Music',
    c: 'Movies',
    d: 'Literature',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What word describes a small settlement, generally one smaller than a village?', 
    a: 'Estuary',
    b: 'Hamlet',
    c: 'Shire',
    d: 'Canton',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of road is raised to allow access across low or swampy ground?', 
    a: 'Parkway',
    b: 'Turnpike',
    c: 'Causeway',
    d: 'Beltway',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'On the show Beavis and Butt-Head, Beavis often transforms into what character?',
    a: 'Stefan',
    b: 'Duffman',
    c: 'Mint-Berry Crunch',
    d: 'Cornholio',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who invented the World Wide Web?', 
    a: 'Tim Berners-Lee',
    b: 'Larry Page',
    c: 'John Fanning',
    d: 'Steve Wozniak',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many bones exist within the human body?', 
    a: '174',
    b: '206',
    c: '410',
    d: '640',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which alcoholic beverage is anise-flavored?', 
    a: 'Sambuca',
    b: 'Pimm\'s',
    c: 'Hpnotiq',
    d: 'Midori',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is the legendary town of Sleepy Hollow located?', 
    a: 'New York',
    b: 'Massachusetts',
    c: 'Rhode Island',
    d: 'New Hampshire',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
